[Music]
foreign
Vietnam and we are very pleased to
receive this financial advisor of the
Year award
so in 2022 Chang achieved a remarkable
result with a total and Norm premium
equipment around 600
000 US Dollars only after nine months
working in Vietnam one of our bank
Partners in Vietnam
so this award mean a lot to Chang and
also to medulla Vietnam as a last but
not least I would like to extend my
gratitude to all medulla college and our
partner within bang in Vietnam and
everyone who have support us Insurance
Specialists
on her journey to bring insurance
solution to customer
and this um Jimenez support switching
has made this journey far more enjoyable
and cooling food I dedicate this award
to all of you thank you and thank you
for this very nice weekend thank you
foreign